TASHA SALGADO

User Experience Designer & Researcher

As a **UX designer**, I combine creative and usability viewpoints that result in real-world solutions for Web and Mobile applications. My user-centered process aids in providing a compelling user experience to improve brand loyalty, customer retention and seamless experiences for users. My goal is to continue to learn all that I can in UX in order to deliver products that will have a positive impact in our society.

tashasalgado.design tasha@tashasalgado.design 510.798.6442

EXPERIENCE

UX Design Apprenticeship ● Bloc

6.2018 - 2.2019

- Developed fundamental Ux Design skills
- Designed web applications using the full UX process, Visual Design and Frontend Development

PUSH | Cloud Storage App

11.2018 - 12.2018

- Designed a simple solution for cloud storage users who need extra security and easier organizing options.
- Figma, Usability Hub, Google Forms, Invision, Draw.io

Health Hooch | E-commerce Design

1.2019 - 2.2019

- Designed a prototype e-commerce store and mobile app for an entreprenuer launching a homemade line of herbal tonics.
- Figma, Usability Hub, Google Forms, Marvel, Flowmapps

Positive Actions International | Re-Design

2.2019-2.2019

- Re-designed to accomplish modern aesthetics, user-friendly navigation and increased conversion.
- Utilized client's web builder combined with custom html

UDEMY & LYNDA COURSES

UX Research for Agile Teams ● Amanda Stockwell Lynda	1.2019
Typography: Choosing & Combining Typefaces • Ina Saltz	2.2019
Photoshop CC 2019 Fundamentals ● Deke McClelland	2.2019
Illustrator CC 2019 Essential Training ● Tom Harmer	2.2019
UI Design Course ● Michael Abehsera	12.2018
Crash Course Design Thinking • Alan Cooper	11.2018

SKILLS

User Research

Persona Creation
Interviews & Surveys
Card Sorting
User-centered Design
Sketching
Wireframing
Protoyping
Competitive Analysis
User Stories
User Flows
Usability Testing
User Interface Design
Basic HTML & CSS
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

Bloc | 2018-2019 UX Design Apprenticeship

TWU | 2018-2020 BS Sociology